afrugalchick.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy/Disclosure Policy - A Frugal Chick

Your privacy is extremely important to me.

Afrugalchick.com, as well as some affiliates, uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, customizes Web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. A “cookie” is a small data text file placed in your browser that allows afrugalchick.com to recognize you each time you visit. These cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and I do not use cookies to collect personal information. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

I will never ask you for credit card information on my site. Please do not send it to me in any form.

Afrugalchick.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. Please read the external sites’ privacy policy before disclosing any information.

Occasionally in the event of giveaways I may request personal information, such as your address. This information will never be shared with anyone.

_It is important to note that this blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorships, paid insertions, or other forms of compensation. The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All opinions stated in this blog belong to its author and no one else. I will only endorse products, companies, and services that I have found worthy of my time and opinion. A Frugal Chick is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to www.amazon.com._

It is important to note that this blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorships, paid insertions, or other forms of compensation. The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All opinions stated in this blog belong to its author and no one else. I will only endorse products, companies, and services that I have found worthy of my time and opinion. A Frugal Chick is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to www.amazon.com.
